<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nabobery</title><link>https://nabobery.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Nabobery</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 10:49:49 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nabobery.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Contact</title><link>https://nabobery.github.io/contact/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 13:20:09 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nabobery.github.io/contact/</guid><description>Contact Me Link to heading Thank you for visiting my blog.
If you have any questions or comments about my content, or if you would like to contact me for any other reason, please feel free to reach out to me using the following contact information :
In addition to the contact information above, you can also find my anime watchlist and ratings on various anime review/list sites such as MyAnimeList and AniList.</description></item><item><title>Hello World!</title><link>https://nabobery.github.io/posts/helloworld/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 10:49:49 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nabobery.github.io/posts/helloworld/</guid><description>Yo, Welcome to my corner of the internet! Link to heading Welcome to my blog! My name is Avinash, a computer science student and problem-solver. My hobbies include listening to music, watching anime, and playing games. On this blog, I will be sharing my journey as a computer science student, my thoughts and reviews on the latest trends and developments in the field of AI, programming, anime and gaming, and also my solutions to the problems I have encountered.</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>https://nabobery.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 10:49:19 +0530</pubDate><guid>https://nabobery.github.io/about/</guid><description>Welcome to my blog! Link to heading My name is Avinash Changrani, and I am a computer science student at IIITDM Kancheepuram. I have always been fascinated by the world of technology and the endless possibilities that it holds. Studying computer science has allowed me to dive deeper into the field, and I have developed a strong passion for problem solving. I believe that understanding and solving problems is the key to creating innovative and impactful solutions.</description></item></channel></rss>